<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Green Card Go</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close</string>

    <string name="disclaimer_text">DISCLAIMER:

Information provided by this GreenCard Go! app on possible methods, if any, for you to obtain a "green card" in order to be a legal permanent resident of the United States is provided as legal information only.  It is absolutely NOT intended to be legal advice.  Every care and effort has been taken to ensure this app contains the latest and most accurate immigration information; however, GreenCard Go! makes no warranty or representation whatsoever, whether express or implied, as to the accuracy of such information.  Any action you take or rely upon after using this app is your own responsibility and GreenCard Go! bears no responsibility or connection to such action.  Consultation with a qualified immigration attorney is highly recommended for definitive advice and guidance for your immigration solutions and planning, such as with the Law Office of Larry L. Doan, GuruImmigration.com, in Los Angeles, California, the creator of this app.

Also, if you have ever been arrested, charged, convicted of a crime anywhere, deported or removed from the US, have multiple unlawful entries into the US, or have had an immigration history in the US but are now living outside, a consultation with an immigration attorney is absolutely a must, as this app only provides information as to what is possible for a person without these grounds of inadmissibility.  With these grounds on your records, it still may be possible for you to obtain a green card but only after being approved for certain difficult waivers or pardons or upon satisfying other conditions.  Only a qualified attorney can advise you on these steps.\n

                                             <b>GENERAL INSTRUCTIONS:</b>\n

This app is for those who are primarily interested in ways to immigrate permanently to the United States, that is, to obtain what is known as a "green card."  Whether you are already in the US or currently outside, obtaining a green card means that you are entitled to live and work permanently in this country.  Although this app does cover some, it is less focused on non-permanent ways to visit or stay in the US as there are numerous such ways, which require a tremendous amount of information-gathering and analysis.  Instead, we believe that users of this app are more interested in permanently immigrating to this country.\n

Note:  This app is not intended for those who already have a green card, strangely enough that is a situation that we sometimes encounter when a person wants to "check" on how they obtained their card.
                                             </string>
    <string name="headre_disclaimer_name">Discaimer</string>
</resources>
